What are you doing?
Don't forget.
You're my fiancée now.
Don't you forget, either.
You promised me.
I'll play your fiancée perfectly.
You have to convince your father to let Zhang Xiaobei go.
You care that much about Zhang Xiaobei?
Think about the Lin family.
Without Prosperity Group's funding,
your hospital would've been ruined long ago.
For him,
is it worth it?
In my father's will,
is there a designated heir?
I'm sorry.
About Chairman Sheng's will,
I can't discuss that with you here.
By the way, the document I asked you to sign last time,
the Supplemental Agreement for the AI project.
Bring it to my office tomorrow.
Well...
You know,
Chairman Sheng sent me to find Zhang Xiaobei
to sign the Supplemental Agreement.
Yes.
The chairman already told me.
From now on, I'm fully in charge of this project.
I want all the files for this project.
Understood.
I'll have someone deliver it tomorrow.
Thank you, Lawyer He.
Don't bother my father with these minor things.
If anything comes up,
just come to me directly.
Goodbye.
So forcing me to transfer the patent...
was ordered by Sheng Shizhong.
And Sheng Yuanzhou didn't even know.
His own son isn't the heir.
This father-son relationship is anything but normal.
This way, please.
Miss Lin.
These are all our new seasonal arrivals.
Take a look.
I'm fine with anything. You pick.
Then we'll take one of each style.
Mr. Sheng is really good to his fiancée.
He's just going through the motions.
I'm just a trophy.
How could that be?
In your eyes,
isn't it just how much he spends on you
that shows how much he loves you?
A man's love for a woman
isn't the amount of money he spends,
it's the proportion he's willing to spend.
These clothes are nothing to you.
So your love
is worthless.
Why don't you try this one?
It just came in yesterday.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Money sure is nice.
It can buy respect and envy,
even love.
Don't you think you look pathetic,
propping yourself up with money?
Not at all.
I'm very happy.
But you...
Acting all high and mighty makes me sick.
Siqi.
What are you doing here?
This dress is so pretty.
Looks like your big day is coming soon.
Stop making fun of me.
I've got enough on my mind.
Others would kill to be in your shoes.
And you're saying you're annoyed?
If you like it,
take it.
Then I'll really take it.
Just kidding.
I'm going to try on the gown first.
See you in a bit.
Isn't that Siqi's bestie?
Why is she acting like that toward me?
Could it be Sheng Yuanzhou and her...
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Sheng, you're really good at putting up with things.
A woman who made you a cuckold,
and you'll still willingly get engaged and marry her.
That's my business.
Who are you to question it?
Given our relationship,
I can at least complain a little, can't I?
I just think you're a poor thing.
Miss Lin.
Please take a look at these styles.
Especially this one,
and the one you just tried on...
Lin Siqi.
I'm going to show you
how ugly the man you chose really is.
Fine.
I'd love to see it.
How exactly do you comfort a "poor thing"?
Treating your friend's fiancé like this...
do you think that's appropriate?
Didn't you call me cheap?
What do I have left to care about?
Do you see it?
This is the man you chose.
Miss Lin,
your fiancé is cheating with your bestie.
Siqi, seeing all this,
must be devastated, right?
This is hilarious.
Stay away from Siqi from now on.
If you dare hurt her,
don't blame me if I get rough with you.
Excuse me, coming through.
Xiaobei.
Siqi.
What's wrong?
I...
Let's go, hurry.
Is something going on?
I'm fine.
Go on. You're going to run out of time.
Hello?
I'm just one intersection away.
I'll be there in a minute.
I'm starving to death waiting here.
Go feed it to the dogs.
I'm definitely filing a complaint.
Give it to me. I'll have it for dinner.
But...
It's what someone else didn't want.
So what?
Didn't we used to
eat canceled orders all the time?
Well...
that doesn't seem right, does it?
Xiaobei.
That day...
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
I believe you.
You must have had your reasons.
You didn't mean to hurt me.
You don't have to worry about me.
Think more about yourself.
Xiaobei.
What are you doing?
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Since you don't even like me,
and you know I don't like you either,
why do you have to do this?
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Siqi isn't your property.
Siqi, she's not your property.
She has the right to choose who she loves.
Who are you to say that?
You impostor.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Can't you just let me go?
You know that
I agreed to the engagement
for Xiaobei and my family.
I can stick to the deal
and play a good wife,
staying by your side.
But even if I'm with you,
my heart and my mind
will only belong to Zhang Xiaobei.
Can you really live like that?
So everything you did was for
him?
You knew it all along,
how important Zhang Xiaobei is to me.
So why keep forcing me to stay?
You're right.
Money can buy a lot of things,
but it can't buy a sincere heart.
So I won't hurt the one I truly love anymore.
I'm sorry.
Siqi made a deal for my sake,
so she had to get engaged to Sheng Yuanzhou.
Siqi.
I'm sorry.
What you just said...
Stop it, it's really embarrassing.
Fine, I won't say it.
But...
I've taken it all to heart.
It's getting late.
I'm going home.
Okay, I'll call you a car.
We'll do it the usual way.
Just give me a ride on your bike.
You sure?
I used to give you rides on my bike?
Of course.
I kinda remember that.
But why does it feel so unfamiliar?
Come on.
Again.
So you liked Siqi all along too.
But sorry, Sheng Yuanzhou.
Siqi loves me.
Before it's too late,
I'll end your engagement to Siqi, no matter what.
Still like a little kid.
Every time it's my birthday,
you always want cake from the hotel.
Siqi.
You're grown up now, getting married.
Dad, it's your birthday today.
Why are you saying that?
Come on, Dad, let's buy a strawberry cake.
It's a limited edition.
Where are we going later?